nameslot.com 2013-06-07

# Nameslot Domain Tools

Privacy Policy for NamesLot

  NamesLot respects and values the privacy of our visitors and members. This privacy policy covers how NamesLot treats personal information collected and received.

  What This Privacy Policy Covers

  This policy covers personal information including personally identifiable information about you like your name or email address. This Privacy Statement does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties that NamesLot does not own or control, or to individuals that NamesLot does not control or manage. Note also that children under 13 are not permitted to use NamesLot. Therefore, NamesLot's privacy policy does not account for children's use of the site. Links to Other Sites

  NamesLot contains links to media and other websites that are not owned or controlled by NamesLot. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. Information Collection and Use

  NamesLot owns a copy of the the personal information of visitors and members collected at NamesLot.com. Members whose data is collected also own a copy of the information about themselves and their own activities with NamesLot. NamesLot's ownership does not mean that it will share or sell your personal information to anyone without your authorization or consent. NamesLot will not share or sell this information with the exception of those terms disclosed in this Privacy Statement.

  NamesLot will aggregate information about users of the site. "Aggregated Information" means information where personally identifying information is removed, and lots of visitors and members data is aggregated together to become statistical information for NamesLot about how the site is used. Aggregated information that is not personally identifying for users is solely owned by NamesLot and is used to improve our services. Statistical information may be shared with other parties.

  Surveys or Contests

  NamesLot may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you decide to participate, we will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice about whether or not to disclose your information. The requested information may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code).

  This information will only be used internally to determine eligibility, notify contest winners, and to measure the success of our efforts. Publicly held contest winners will be labeled on the NamesLot site in public ways through their user ID's or handles.

  General Information

  NamesLot collects personal information upon registration. When you register we ask for your email address and certain optional information such as your name. NamesLot automatically collects and records information from your browser, including your IP address, cookie, and the page you request. IP Addresses are disclosed by your browser as you view a web page.

  Third Party Advertisers

  Advertisements appearing on NamesLot may be delivered by a third party. For information about advertisers on NamesLot, please visit their websites through links provided at the advertisements on NamesLot.

  Information Sharing and Disclosure

  NamesLot allows many activities for member that will result in revealing of some information about your activities to others, including visitors and members. For example, these activities might include editing a media record, posting a comment, making a playlist or sending a message. When you "write" something in NamesLot, your NamesLot ID handle or alias that you are posting under will be visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. NamesLot is not responsible for the messages you post or receive, either publicly or through the NamesLot messaging system.

  Generally, NamesLot will not share your personal information with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except to provide products or services you've requested and in the following circumstances:

  * NamesLot may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
* It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of NamesLot's terms of use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.  
* We will transfer information about you if NamesLot is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, NamesLot will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the NamesLot web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  Choice/Opt-out

  At any time, you can change your NamesLot account information. To delete your account send an PM to the admin on the forum and your account will be disabled.However, please note that some personal information may need to be maintained if it is for billing or required by law. Some employees will have access to our personal information, but this will be limited to those whose jobs are dependent on such information.

  Changes in this Privacy Policy

  This Privacy Statement is a living document. NamesLot may update this policy at any time for any reason. If we significantly change how we handle personal information, we will notify the primary email address specified in your NamesLot account. We will also placing a notice on our blog and on the Privacy page at NamesLot.com/privacy.

  If you have questions or suggestions please use you the feedback form or you can contact us at admin@NamesLot.com
